Lovell, Malcolm R., Jr. Papers 6119
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Malcolm R. Lovell, Jr. Papers
1990-1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Lovell, Malcolm R., Jr.
6119
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Papers.
5806221
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 23, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining; Lovell, Malcolm Read, 1921-; Collective Bargaining Forum -- Archives
5806221
- CBF statement, staff meeting notes, CBF minutes of meetings, manuscripts, routine correspondence.. (Box 1)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CBF Principals and Stall, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CBF Retreat Sept. 21-22, 1993 Annapolis, MD (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CBF Staff Retreat Sept. 21-22, 1993 Annapolis, MD Jim's Folder (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CBF Principals Meeting - Nov. 17, 1994 City Tavern Club (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CBF Papers and Correp. 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum Nov. 6, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum January 17and18, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum June 22-23, 1995, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CBF Paper Toward A New Social Contrac in Employment Relations 1996,1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CBF Germany Trip - Oct. 10-17, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CBF - Germany Works Councils Trip, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CBF 1997,1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum 1996and 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CBF Minutes Staff Working Group 1089-1992, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CBF Staff Meeting Jan. 15, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Collective Bargaining Forum Working Group Meeting, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - CBF Financial 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CBF Health Care, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Statement CBF, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CBF Staff March 18, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Guidelines For Health Care Reform CBF (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Occupational Health and Safety Forum: routine correspondence, meeting minutes, newsletters and brochures from outside sources.. (Box 2)
  - OSHF AD Hoc Group-Aug 10-2pm, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - OHSF- December 14, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Occupationsl Safety & Health Forum April 16, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Recruitments OS & HF, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Minutes- Occupational Health & Safety Forum, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Occupational Health & Safety Forum, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vichiu OS and HF Files (Folder 1 of 2), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vichiu OS and HF Files (Folder 2 of 2), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Occupational Health & Safety Forum- Financials, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Occupational Health & Safety Forum, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Occupational Health & Safety Forum - Newspaper Clippings, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Occupational Healthand Safety Forum (Folder 1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Occupational Healthand Safety Forum (Folder 2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Docs. Relating to Labor and Unions, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Documents about Labor, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Docs. Relating to the IRRA, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Occupational Health & Safety Forum, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Retreat - OSHF October 19, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Occupational Health and Safety Forum, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - OSHF Retreat 10/19/93 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Docs. Relating to the IRRA, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- CBF member recruitment, routine correspondence, financials for 1993, meeting records. One file with CBF minutes from 1985-88.. (Box 3)
  - CBF Minutes 1985-88, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Options for Labor Policy CBF, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - National Planning Association, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - CBF Staff Meeting Sept. 1, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - CBF Meeting- Canceled, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - CBF Principals City Tavern Club May 25, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum Dinner- Cancelled, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CBF Financial 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CBF Financial 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CBF Financial, 1985-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Membership Recruitment CBF, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - CBF Principals Meeting January 25, 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - CBF Poll - Oct/ Nov., 1997 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CBF Statement on Worker-Management Rel. June 2, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - CBF Statement on American Workplace July 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - CBF Articles & Newsclippings, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CBF Principals City Tavern Club March 7, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - CBF MRL Old Parest Membership, 1985-1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum Cancelled May 21, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - CBF Minutes Principals 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CBF Papers & Corres. 1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - CBF Correspondence 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- CBF White House meeting with VP Al Gore records and routine correspondence, staff working group files, manuscript.. (Box 4)
  - Cbf 1995, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CBF 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CBF Correspondence 1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bargaining nine (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum 1991 and Earlier, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CBF Minutes Principals, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CBF White House Meeting 4-29-99, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CBF 1999 5/92 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - CBF Minutes Staff Working Group, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - CBF Staff Meeting Jan. 15, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - CBF - Paper April 1997 "Principles for a New Employment Relationship", 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CBF 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Collective Bargaining Forum - Staff December 2, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CBf Principals City Tavern Club May 17, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - CBF Working Group Meeting June 22 1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - CBF Working Group May 11, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Report and Recommendations, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - CBF Correspondence 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Staff meeting minutes, 1995 financials, GAO pubs, published articles, DOL brochures,.. (Box 5)
  - CBF 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CBF Financial 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - CBF 10/1/98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Draltsy CBF Paper 4-15-99 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CBF Staff Meeting April 23and30 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Articles on Labor and The Business Roundtable, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Part Two* The Long Battle for Manpower Policy Reform (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Occupational Safety & Health, Labor Management Commitment: A Compact for Change and New Directions for Labor and Management, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)